[
    {
        "question": "Black",
        "choice1": "verde",
        "choice2": "rosado",
        "choice3": "negro",
        "choice4": "anaranjado",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Brown",
        "choice1": "blanco",
        "choice2": "marrón / café",
        "choice3": "morado / púrpura",
        "choice4": "amarillo",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Grey",
        "choice1": "gris",
        "choice2": "amarillo",
        "choice3": "morado / púrpura",
        "choice4": "negro",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "White",
        "choice1": "blanco",
        "choice2": "verde",
        "choice3": "rojo",
        "choice4": "gris",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Yellow",
        "choice1": "gris",
        "choice2": "amarillo",
        "choice3": "blanco",
        "choice4": "morado / púrpura",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Orange",
        "choice1": "marrón / café",
        "choice2": "azul",
        "choice3": "verde",
        "choice4": "anaranjado",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Red",
        "choice1": "amarillo",
        "choice2": "rojo",
        "choice3": "rosado",
        "choice4": "azul",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Pink",
        "choice1": "gris",
        "choice2": "marrón / café",
        "choice3": "rosado",
        "choice4": "azul",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Purple",
        "choice1": "anaranjado",
        "choice2": "morado / púrpura",
        "choice3": "negro",
        "choice4": "rojo",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Blue",
        "choice1": "negro",
        "choice2": "anaranjado",
        "choice3": "azul",
        "choice4": "blanco",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Green",
        "choice1": "rosado",
        "choice2": "verde",
        "choice3": "azul",
        "choice4": "marrón / café",
        "answer": 2
    }
]